The bride is back for the final cut.
Kill Bill: Vol. 2 is a action, crime, thriller
film directed by Quentin Tarantino.
The Bride unwaveringly continues on her roaring rampage of revenge against the
band of assassins who had tried to kill her and her unborn child.
She visits each of her former associates one-by-one, checking off the victims on her
Death List Five until there's nothing left to do … but kill Bill.
Beatrix Kiddo / The Bride / 'Black Mamba' / Mommy, played by Uma Thurman.
Bill 'Snake Charmer', played by David Carradine.
Elle Driver 'California Mountain Snake', played by Daryl Hannah.
Budd 'Sidewinder', played by Michael Madsen.
Johnny Mo / Pai Mei, played by Gordon Liu Chia-Hui.
Earl McGraw / Esteban Vihaio, played by Michael Parks.
Kill Bill Vol.
2 Original Soundtrack is the soundtrack to the 2004 film Kill Bill: Volume 2.
Released on April 13, 2004, it reached #58 on the Billboard 200 and
#2 on the Billboard soundtracks chart in the US.
It also reached the ARIA Top 50 album charts in Australia.
It was orchestrated by Tarantino's fellow filmmaker and personal friend
Robert Rodriguez, as well as RZA from the Wu-Tang Clan.
The film explores themes of daughter, martial arts,
kung fu, showdown, right and justice.
The tone is intense.